songsjumbo.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | SongsJumbo

This website Privacy Policy is incorporated herein by reference and may be posted and applicable to specific services, governs your use of the this website and are collectively referred to as the "Privacy Policy Agreement".  
We may modify this Privacy Policy Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services, indicates your acceptance of the Agreement.

We use third party services such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/), [AddThis](http://www.addthis.com/privacy) to measure usage and analyze trends, administer the website and collect information for its databases.

Third-party websites linked to SongsJumbo are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These websites may collect personally identifiable information about you and place a cookie on your browser. SongsJumbo is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party websites and companies.

SongsJumbo is not responsible if you volunteer personal information online that is accessible to the public. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties or it may be used in a manner that violates the law, your personal privacy or your safety. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed.

In the event that SongsJumbo  is acquired or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control. In the unlikely event of our insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, SongsJumbo may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred or used.
